[Netero] This is a tomb.
Yours, as a matter of fact.
Grateful for everything
that's led me to this point,
and to you.
[opening theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[singer singing in English]
ZERO X AND X ROSE
[blows striking]
[gasps]
[dramatic music playing]
…unreserved admiration
for his enemy.
[Netero] Hmm.
[King] That's it.
The attack begins only after
he brings his hands together,
and from what I can tell
that's the only motion
that surpasses my speed.
Such wasteful movement
I won't waste precious time
to guess what drove him to this.
[thudding]
[dramatic music playing]
of time and effort on your part,
and I recognize that.
[Netero] All that, and there's
barely a scratch on him.
Well, I expected as much.
You are a rare example
of one who's transcended that limit.
[Netero] Why, you little…
An insect like you
should never talk down to humans!
[gasps]
If the 100-Type Guanyin Bodhisattva
Once I've identified
all of the combinations
of potential plays,
However, while he may have
a finite number of attack patterns,
the number of combinations
in which they can be used
may as well be infinite.
If I can just ascertain
the characteristics of his rhythm,
then I stand a fair chance of predicting
which patterns
he's most likely to select.
but I will have to thread it
with utmost precision.
That's what it'll take
to pierce my target.
This may be a heavy undertaking.
I can do this!
Old soldier, I beg of you.
It will happen soon,
so don't collapse before then.
[laughs]
I can't make a single wrong move.
One misstep, and his speed
won't leave enough time
to unleash my next hand,
This is a battle of endurance,
That's what you're thinking,
isn't it, King of Ants?
Fine, then.
I'll checkmate you shortly.
[Netero] Checkmate me if you can,
but I won't make it easy.
I'll show you the Zero Hand!
Stop the bleeding,
and tell me what my name is.
You have done well…
for a human, of course.
-[Netero grunts]
-[gasps]
You really think I'll die?
It was one lucky punch,
so don't get cocky.
This battle is only beginning.
You have truly earned my admiration.
With everything that's happened thus far,
your spirit has yet to diminish.
while not exactly bad,
was not the best choice.
I learned the art
of anticipating an enemy's actions.
Your subconscious bias
against certain patterns
gives me insight
into the otherwise limitless options
you have at your disposal,
which gives me the edge.
did not even last a full minute.
[Netero] This is it,
the last time in my life!
[narrator] As he released
his 100-Type Guanyin Bodhisattva,
Netero's resolve heightened
his physical and mental senses.
causing sparks that
showered them like fountains.
the imperceptible bias
in Netero's moves,
a bias so slight it couldn't
even be called a habit.
After using his body to bear the brunt
of Netero's unrelenting attacks,
[intense music playing]
What is it? What is my name?
[laughs]
The King of the Ants.
I don't need arms to pray.
Far from it.
Huh?
[chorus vocalizing]
[Netero] Prayer is an action of the heart.
and the wish then bears fruit.
that he changed his direction.
The entirety of Netero's aura
was transformed into a light
much like a dazzling star,
[Netero groaning]
[groans]
[King] Truly the pinnacle of mankind.
I freely admit it was a brilliant attack.
[Netero] Zero wasn't enough?
[King] I was born
to be the King of the Ants,
the crowning glory of life.
I represent the instinctive hope
long nurtured by my species,
a species that continues
to evolve for my sake.
You are but one lowly human, not a king.
I am the King that bears
the fate of his kind,
is focused on the end point
of all evolution.
That end point is me.
with a preserve
for a permanent settlement.
We'll consider both quality and quantity
[narrator] The King could not
savor his name
as it fell from the old man's lips,
an old man who should, by all rights,
be trembling before him,
yet Netero did not.
[imperceptible]
within the human heart.
[narrator] Just then,
the King felt true fear
for the first time.
made it clear he meant every single word.
[explosion]
[closing theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[Gon] I'll believe in my friends,
no matter what.
[Gon and Killua]
Thank you, Chairman Netero.
[singer singing in Japanese]